

NGUYỄN HỮU THẮNG

Bế Văn Đàn, Tp. Đà Nẵng

0906.401.845

▼ thangnh0511@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/thang-nh

Hi, I'm Nguyen Huu Thang.

Working in the IT field is my desire. Fortunately, I was worked for approximately 2 years on an Accounting and ERP company helps digital transformation for businesses since I had already graduated from university. That is a great time for me to approach and learning more both knowledge and soft skills. I believe with my knowledge and skills base on IT and economics, also with the passion and serious attitude on working will help me get rapid high level in the coming years.

EDUCATION

DA NANG UNIVERSITY OF ECONOMICS

Management Information System

2015 - 2019

EXPERIENCES

BUSINESS ANALYST

Fast - Accounting & ERP Software

2019 - 2021

Identify problems within a business and describe requirements.

Communicate and persuade with stakeholder for solution and

benefits of Digital transformation for business.

Writing scope and schedule of project

Implement system and run training sessions.

COPYWRITER & DESIGNER

Marketing Teams

2018 - 2019

Design media publications for website and Facebook Making schedule post on the facebook platform

Team work in order to have creative ads content

Editing promotional video, short animation videos, product

photography

Writing content for SEO

SKILLS

TECHNICAL & TOOLS

SQL Server Good
HTML/CSS Good
Computer Networking Usable
Adobe Creative Suite Good
Microsoft Office Suite Good

SOFT SKILLS

English

Time & Work management

Communication

Team work

Self-study

Self-motivate

CERTIFICATES

Microsoft Office Specialist Excel 2017

#90039920

Google UX design

Foundations of User Experience (UX) Design

Start the UX Design Process: Empathize, Define, and Ideate

Build Wireframes and Low-Fidelity Prototypes

HOBBIES







